Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part Two
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Autograph Items by Category, 1666-1961; Series I; 12.1; (32 boxes)
  - LEGAL FIGURES
    - Rawlinson, Christopher, Sir, 1806-1888, 1876 (Box 13, Folder 659)
    - Reformatory and Refuge Union, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 660)
    - Reiff, Walter L., 1903 (Box 13, Folder 661)
    - Rigby, John, Sir, 1834-1901, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 662)
    - Ritchie, Charles Thomson, Sir, 1838- 1906, 1901 (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - Russell of Killowen, Charles Russell, Baron, 1832-1900, undated (Box 13, Folder 664)
    - Sargent, John G. (John Garibaldi), 1860-1939, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 665)
    - Selwyn, Charles Jasper, Sir, 1813-1869, 1861-67 (Box 13, Folder 666)
    - Seymour, William Digby, 1822-1895, 1853, undated (Box 13, Folder 667)
    - Shaw-Lefevre, John George, Sir, 1797- 1879, 1837-57 (Box 13, Folder 668)
    - Shee, William, 1804-1868, 1853-58, undated (Box 13, Folder 669)
    - Sleigh, W. Campbell (William Campbell), 1818-1887, 1852-67 (Box 13, Folder 670)
    - Smith, Archibald, Levis, Sir, 1836- 1901, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 671)
    - Starkie, Thomas, 1782-1849, 1847 (Box 13, Folder 672)
    - Stirling, James, Sir, 1836-1916, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 673)
    - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir, 1795-1854, 1842-51 (Box 13, Folder 674)
    - Thesiger, Alfred Henry, 1838-1880, 1879, undated (Box 13, Folder 675)
    - Thesiger, Edward, Sir, 1842-1928, 1867-96 (Box 13, Folder 676)
    - Thring, Henry Thring, Baron, 1818-1907, 1888-90 (Box 13, Folder 677)
    - Tomlins, Thomas Edlyne, Sir, 1762-1841, 1837 (Box 13, Folder 678)
    - Turner, George James, Sir, 1798-1867, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 679)
    - Twiss, Travers, Sir, 1809-1897, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 680)
    - Vaughan, John, Sir, 1769-1839, 1800 (Box 13, Folder 681)
    - Vincent, C.E. Howard (Charles Edward Howard), 1850-1908, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 682)
    - Waite, Morrison R. (Morrison Renwick), 1816-1888, undated (Box 13, Folder 683)
    - Westlake, John, 1828-1913, 1875 (Box 13, Folder 684)
    - Wilkins, Charles, undated (Box 13, Folder 685)
    - Williams, Montagu Stephen, 1835-1892, 1891, undated (Box 13, Folder 686)
    - Williams, Watkin, 1880-83 (Box 13, Folder 687)
    - Woolrych, Humphry W. (Humphry William), 1795-1871, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 688)
    - Wyndham, Wadham, Sir, 1610-1668, undated (Box 13, Folder 689)
  - MILITARY FIGURES
    - Benson, William Shepherd, 1855-1932, undated (Box 14, Folder 690)
    - Beresford, Charles William De la Poer Beresford, Baron, 1846-1919, undated (Box 14, Folder 691)
    - Brownlow, John Cust, Earl, 1779-1853, 1848 (Box 14, Folder 692)
    - Chelmsford, Frederic Augustus Thesiger, Baron, 1827-1905, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 693)
    - Craven, William Craven, Earl of, 1606- 1697, 1666 (Box 14, Folder 694)
    - Custer, Elizabeth Baron, 1842-1933, 1888-1916, undated (Box 14, Folder 695)
    - Dalhousie, James Andrew Brown Ramsay, Marquis, of, 1812-1860, 1851 (Box 14, Folder 696)
    - FitzHardinge, Maurice Frederick FitzHardinge Berkeley, Baron, 1788- 1867, 1857 (Box 14, Folder 697)
    - Grafton, Augustus FitzRoy, Duke of, 1821-1918, 1892-99 (Box 14, Folder 698)
    - Hardinge, Henry Hardinge, Viscount, 1785-1856, undated (Box 14, Folder 699)
    - Knapp, H.S., undated (Box 14, Folder 700)
    - Lee, Mary Custis, 1835-1918, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 701)
    - Logan, John A., 1873 (Box 14, Folder 702)
    - Maclear, John Pearse, 1830-1907, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 703)
    - Prim y Prats, Juan, marques de los Castillejos, 1814-1870, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 704)
    - Probyn, Dighton MacNaghtan, Sir, 1833- 1924, 1891 (Box 14, Folder 705)
    - Raglan, Fitzroy Somerset, Lord, 1788- 1855, 1826 (Box 14, Folder 706)
    - Silliman, Gold Selleck, 1732-1790, 1780 (Box 14, Folder 707)
  - MUSICIANS
    - Adams, Stephen, 1845-1913, 1909 (Box 15, Folder 708)
    - Albani, Emma, Dame, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 709)
    - Armstrong, Harry, 1879-1951, undated (Box 15, Folder 710)
    - Barnett, John, 1802-1890, undated (Box 15, Folder 711)
    - Benedict, Julius, Sir, 1804-1885, undated (Box 15, Folder 712)
    - Bennett, William Sterndale, Sir, 1816- 1875, 1865-1871 (Box 15, Folder 713)
    - Berger, Francesco, 1834-1933, undated (Box 15, Folder 714)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah, 1844-1923, undated (Box 15, Folder 715)
    - Bishop, Anna, 1810-1884, undated (Box 15, Folder 716)
    - Bispham, David, 1857-1921, undated (Box 15, Folder 717)
    - Blagrove, Charles, undated (Box 15, Folder 718)
    - Blewitt, Jonathan, 1782-1853, undated (Box 15, Folder 719)
    - Blumenthal, Jacques, 1829-1908, 1880s (Box 15, Folder 720)
    - Borwick, Leonard, 1868-1925, 1890 (Box 15, Folder 721)
    - Brandram, Rosina, 1846-1907, undated (Box 15, Folder 722)
    - Brema, Marie, Miss, 1856-1925, 1909 (Box 15, Folder 723)
    - Bridge, Frederick, Sir, 1844-1924, undated (Box 15, Folder 724)
    - Broadwood, John and Sons, 1868 (Box 15, Folder 725)
    - Bucalosi, Ernest, 1869 (Box 15, Folder 726)
    - Butt, Clara, Dame, 1873-1936, undated (Box 15, Folder 727)
    - Cellier, Alfred, 1844-1891, 1881 (Box 15, Folder 728)
    - Chevallier, Albert, 1861-1923, undated (Box 15, Folder 729)
    - Chirgwin, G.H., 1909 (Box 15, Folder 730)
    - Cole, Blanche, undated (Box 15, Folder 731)
    - Cooke, T. (Thomas), 1792-1848, undated (Box 15, Folder 732)
    - Costa, Michael, Sir, 1808-1884, 1848-1874 (Box 15, Folder 733)
    - Cotogni, Antonio, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 734)
    - Crossley, Ada, 1874-1929, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 735)
    - Crystal Palace, Programme, 1881 (Box 15, Folder 736)
    - Cummings, William Hayman, 1831-1915, 1887 (Box 15, Folder 737)
    - Dannrouther, Daniel, 1844-1905, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 738)
    - Davies, Benjamin, 1858-1943, 1897 (Box 15, Folder 739)
    - Davies, Fanny, 1861-1934, 1890s (Box 15, Folder 740)
    - Davies, Mary, 1855-1930, 1888-1892 (Box 15, Folder 741)
    - Distinn, John, undated (Box 15, Folder 742)
    - Dolby, Charlotte Helen, 1821-1885, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 743)
    - Dulcken, Marie Louise, undated (Box 15, Folder 744)
    - Elliott, G.H., undated (Box 15, Folder 745)
    - Elvey, George, Sir, 1816-1893, 1874 (Box 15, Folder 746)
    - Elvey, Stephen, 1805-1860, undated (Box 15, Folder 747)
    - Ernst, Heinrich Wilhelm, 1814-1865, undated (Box 15, Folder 748)
    - Eyre, Alfred J., 1853-1919, undated (Box 15, Folder 749)
    - Farningham, Marianne, 1834-1909, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 750)
    - Fiorentini, Claudina, 1850 (Box 15, Folder 751)
    - Fitzwilliam, Edward, 1824-1857, 1854 (Box 15, Folder 752)
    - Flowers, George French, 1811-1872, 1844 (Box 15, Folder 753)
    - Gabriel, Virginia, 1825-1877, undated (Box 15, Folder 754)
    - Goddard, Arabella, 1836-1922, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 755)
    - Goldschmidt, Otto, 1829-1907, 1895 (Box 15, Folder 756)
    - Grain, Corney, 1844-1895, undated (Box 15, Folder 757)
    - Green, Richard, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 758)
    - Grove, George, Sir, 1820-1900, 1886 (Box 15, Folder 759)
    - Hardelot, Guy d'. 1858-1936, 1906 (Box 15, Folder 760)
    - Joachim, Joseph, 1831-1907, undated (Box 15, Folder 761)
    - Lemmens-Sherrington, Helen, 1834-1906, undated (Box 15, Folder 762)
    - Lloyd, Edward, 1845-1927, 1882 (Box 15, Folder 763)
    - London Institution, admittance ticket, 1874 (Box 15, Folder 764)
    - MacFarren, Walter Cecil, 1826-1905, undated (Box 16, Folder 765)
    - Mackenzie, Alexander Campbell, Sir, 1847-1935, undated (Box 16, Folder 766)
    - Manns, Augustus, Sir, 1825-1907, undated (Box 16, Folder 767)
    - Montgomery, James, 1771-1854, 1844 (Box 16, Folder 768)
    - Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880, 1863 (Box 16, Folder 769)
    - Parepa-Rosa, Euphrosne, 1836-1874, 1869 (Box 16, Folder 770)
    - Parry, C. Hubert H. (Charles Hubert Hastings), 1848-1918, 1889-1900 (Box 16, Folder 771)
    - Patti, Adelina, 1843-1919, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 772)
    - Pinsuti, Ciro, 1829-1888, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 773)
    - Rodwell, G. Herbert (George Herbert), 1800-1852, 1843, undated (Box 16, Folder 774)
    - Royal Italian Opera, Programme, 1864 (Box 16, Folder 775)
    - Sainton, P.C., 1813-1890, 1882 (Box 16, Folder 776)
    - Schulz-Curtius, Alfred, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 777)
    - Scott-Gatty, Alfred, 1847-1918, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 778)
    - Seguin, William Henry, 1814-1850, undated (Box 16, Folder 779)
    - Silas, Edouard, 1827-1909, 1871 (Box 16, Folder 780)
    - Sinclair, George Robertson, 1863-1917, 1886-94, undated (Box 16, Folder 781)
    - Sinicoa, M., undated (Box 16, Folder 782)
    - Sloper, Edward Hugh Lindsay, 1826-1887, 1862-85 (Box 16, Folder 783)
    - Smart, Henry Thomas, 1813-1879, 1868-72 (Box 16, Folder 784)
    - Smith, Montem, 1828-1891, 1865-73 (Box 16, Folder 785)
    - Smith, Seymour, 1877 (Box 16, Folder 786)
    - Spence, Anne, undated (Box 16, Folder 787)
    - Squire, W.H. (William Henry), 1871- 1963, 1897, undated (Box 16, Folder 788)
    - Stainer, John, Sir, 1840-1901, 1881-1901, undated (Box 16, Folder 789)
    - Stanford, Charles Villiers, Sir, 1852- 1924, undated (Box 16, Folder 790)
    - Stanton-Dolby, Charlotte H., 1821-1855, undated (Box 16, Folder 791)
    - Steggall, Charles, 1826-1905, 1877 (Box 16, Folder 792)
    - Steggall, Reginald, 1867-1938, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 793)
    - Sterling, Antoinette, Mrs., 1850-1906, undated (Box 16, Folder 794)
    - Stewart, Robert, Sir, 1825-1894, 1884 (Box 16, Folder 795)
    - Swain, Charles, 1801-1874, 1847 (Box 16, Folder 796)
    - Templeton, John, 1802-1886, 1843 (Box 16, Folder 797)
    - Thomas, John, 1795-1871, 1861 (Box 16, Folder 798)
    - Thomas, John, 1826-1913, 1870 (Box 16, Folder 799)
    - Thomas, Lewis William, 1826-1896, 1865 (Box 16, Folder 800)
    - Trans-Atlantic Steamship Souvenir, including signatures of Olga Nethersole, E. Calve, De Roszke, etc., undated (Box 16, Folder 801)
    - Trust, Helen, Mrs., 1897 (Box 16, Folder 802)
    - Trust, Henry J., undated (Box 16, Folder 803)
    - Tullutti, A. Bettini, 1819-1893, 1880 (Box 16, Folder 804)
    - Turle, James, 1802-1882, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 805)
    - Van Biene, Auguste, b. 1845, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 806)
    - Waldegrave, Frances Braham, Countess, 1836-1879, undated (Box 16, Folder 807)
    - Weatherley, Frederic Edward, 1848-1929, 1881-94, undated (Box 16, Folder 808)
    - Webber, Amherst, 1867-1946, 1901 (Box 16, Folder 809)
    - Webber, Byron, 1900-05, undated (Box 16, Folder 810)
    - Weiss, W.H. (Willoughby Hunter), 1820- 1867 (Box 16, Folder 811)
    - Wellesley, Fred, 1887-91 (Box 16, Folder 812)
    - Welsh, Thomas, ca. 1780-1848, 1840 (Box 16, Folder 813)
    - Werner, Louis B., b. 1856, undated (Box 16, Folder 814)
    - Wesley, Samuel Sebastian, 1810-1876, 1870 (Box 16, Folder 815)
    - Westbrook, William Joseph, 1834-1894, 1892 (Box 16, Folder 816)
    - White, Maude Valerie, 1853-1937, 1890-92, undated (Box 16, Folder 817)
    - Williams, Anna, 1845-1924, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 818)
    - Wolff, Johannes, 1862-1940, 1894-98, undated (Box 16, Folder 819)
    - Wood, Henry Joseph, Sir, 1869-1944, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 820)
    - Wright, Ellen, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 821)
    - Wynne, Sarah Edith, 1842-1897, undated (Box 16, Folder 822)
  - NOBILITY
    - Ailesbury, Ernest Brudenell-Bruce III, Marquess, 1811-1886, 1881, undated (Box 17, Folder 823)
    - Alvanley, William Arden, Baron, 1789- 1849, 1824-40, undated (Box 17, Folder 824)
    - Annesley, Hugh Annesley, Earl, 1831- 1908, undated (Box 17, Folder 825)
    - Argyll, John Douglas Sutherland Campbell, Duke of, 1845-1914, 1875 (Box 17, Folder 826)
    - Ashburnham, Bertram Ashburnham, Earl of, 1787-1878, 1872, undated (Box 17, Folder 827)
    - Ashburnham, John Ashburnham, Baron, 1655-1709, undated (Box 17, Folder 828)
    - Atholl, John James Hugh Henry Stuart- Murray, Duke of, 1840-1917, 1883 (Box 17, Folder 829)
    - Augusta, Duchess of Cambirdge, 1797- 1889, 1864, undated (Box 17, Folder 830)
    - Aumale, Henri d'Orleans, duc d', 1822- 1897, 1862-87 (Box 17, Folder 831)
    - Bagot, William Bagot, Baron, 1773-1856, 1843 (Box 17, Folder 832)
    - Bath, Frances Isabella Catherine Vesey Thynne, Marchioness of, 1840-1915, 1886 (Box 17, Folder 833)
    - Beauchamp, Frederick Lygon, Earl, 1830-1891, 1888 (Box 17, Folder 834)
    - Beaufort, Henry Adelbert FitzRoy Somerset, Duke of, 1847-1924, 1900 (Box 17, Folder 835)
    - Beaufort, Henry Charles FitzRoy Somerset, Duke of, 1824-1899, 1858-94 (Box 17, Folder 836)
    - Bedford, Francis Charles Hastings Russell, Duke of, 1819-1891, 1876, undated (Box 17, Folder 837)
    - Bedford, Francis Russell, Duke of, 1788-1861, 1858, undated (Box 17, Folder 838)
    - Bedford, George Russell, Duke of, 1852-1893, 1874 (Box 17, Folder 839)
    - Bedford, Herbrand Arthur Russell, Duke of, 1858-1940, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 840)
    - Bedford, William Russell, Duke of, 1809-1872, 1837-68 (Box 17, Folder 841)
    - Berkeley, Mary, Countess of, 1767?- 1844, undated (Box 17, Folder 842)
    - Boston, George Ives Irby, Baron, 1802- 1869, 1865 (Box 17, Folder 843)
    - Bradford, Selina Louisa Forester Bridgman, Countess of, d. 1894, 1875 (Box 17, Folder 844)
    - Breadalbane, Gavin Campbell, Marquess, 1851-1922, 1886 (Box 17, Folder 845)
    - Buchan, Henry David Erskine, Earl, 1783-1857, undated (Box 17, Folder 846)
    - Buckinghamshire, George Robert Hobart- Hampden, Earl of, 1789-1849, 1852 (Box 17, Folder 847)
    - Cardigan, Robert Brudenell, Earl, 1769-1837, 1822 (Box 17, Folder 848)
    - Chesterfield, Anne Elizabeth Weld- Forester Stanhope, Countess of, 1802- 1885, undated (Box 17, Folder 849)
    - Chesterfield, George Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1866, undated (Box 17, Folder 850)
    - De L'Isle and Dudley, Philip Sidney, Baron, 1828-1898, undated (Box 17, Folder 851)
    - De Saumarez, James St. Vincent Saumarez, 1843-1937, undated (Box 17, Folder 852)
    - Du Cane, Georgiana Susan, Lady, b. 1838, undated (Box 17, Folder 853)
    - Erdody, Countess, 1899-1900, undated (Box 17, Folder 854)
    - Eugenie, Empress, Countess of Napoleon III, Emperor of the French, 1826-1920, 1856-69, undated (Box 17, Folder 855)
    - Exeter, Brownlow Cecil, Marquess of, 1795-1867, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 856)
    - Exeter, Brownlow Henry George Cecil, Marquess of, 1849-1898, 1883 (Box 17, Folder 857)
    - Exeter, Henry Cecil, Marquess of, 1754-1804, 1795-1803 (Box 17, Folder 858)
    - Falmouth, Evelyn Edward Thomas Boscawen, Viscount, 1847-1918, 1899 (Box 17, Folder 859)
    - FitzWilliam, William Thomas Spencer Wentworth-FitzWilliam, Earl, 1815-1902, 1885 (Box 17, Folder 860)
    - Grosvenor, Dora Mina Erskine-Wemyss, Lady, 1856-1894, 1890 (Box 17, Folder 861)
    - Grosvenor, Victor Alexander Grosvenor, Earl, 1853-1884, 1860, undated (Box 17, Folder 862)
    - Liverpool, Louisa Theodosia Hervey Jenkinson, Countess, d. 1821, undated (Box 17, Folder 863)
    - Lochiel, Elizabeth Cameron, Lady, b. 1846, 1886 (Box 17, Folder 864)
    - Montagu, George Brudenell Montagu, Duke of, 1712-1790, 1779 (Box 17, Folder 865)
    - Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852, undated (Box 17, Folder 866)
    - Paris, Louis Philippe Albert d'Orleans, comte de, 1838-1894, undated (Box 17, Folder 867)
    - Portsmouth, Anne Hanson Wallop, Countess of, undated (Box 17, Folder 868)
    - Reading, Rufus Daniel Isaacs, Marquess of, 1860-1935, undated (Box 17, Folder 869)
    - Russell, William, Lord, 1767-1840, 1814-28, undated (Box 17, Folder 870)
    - Vinesbeck, Baron, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 871)
    - Westminster, Hugh Lupus Grosvenor, Duke of, 1825-1899, 1861-93, undated (Box 17, Folder 872)
    - Yarborough, Charles Alfred Worsley Pelham, Earl, 1859-1936, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 873)
  - POLITICAL FIGURES
    - Aberdare, Henry Austen Bruce, Baron, 1815-1895, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 874)
    - Aberdeen, George Hamilton Gordon, Earl of, 1784-1860, undated (Box 18, Folder 875)
    - Acland, Charles Thomas Dyke, Sir, 1842-1919, undated (Box 18, Folder 876)
    - Alington, Henry Gerard Stuart, Baron, 1825-1904, 1876, undated (Box 18, Folder 877)
    - Allendale, Wentworth Blackett Beaumont, Baron, 1829-1907, 1857-71 (Box 18, Folder 878)
    - Amherst of Arracan, William Pitt Amherst, Earl, 1773-1857, 1842 (Box 18, Folder 879)
    - Andrassy, Gyula, grof, 1823-1890, undated (Box 18, Folder 880)
    - Antonelli, Giacomo, 1806-1876, undated (Box 18, Folder 881)
    - Argyll, George Douglas Campbell, Duke of, 1823-1900, 1841-99 (Box 18, Folder 882)
    - Ashburton, Alexander Baring, Baron, 1774-1848, 1816-41 (Box 18, Folder 883)
    - Ashburton, William Bingham Baring, Baron, 1799-1864, 1844-49 (Box 18, Folder 884)
    - Asquith, H.H. (Herbert Henry), 1852- 1928, 1904-07 (Box 18, Folder 885)
    - Astor, Waldorf Astor, Viscount, 1879- 1952, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 886)
    - Auckland, George Eden, Earl of, 1784- 1849, 1842-46 (Box 18, Folder 887)
    - Ayrton, Acton Smee, 1816-1886, undated (Box 18, Folder 888)
    - Baden-Powell, George Smyth, Sir, 1847- 1898, 1896 (Box 18, Folder 889)
    - Bagehot, Walter, 1826-1877, undated (Box 18, Folder 890)
    - Baillie, George (also includes Edgcumbe, Richard Edgcumbe, Baron, 1680-1758), 1721 (Box 18, Folder 891)
    - Baines, Edward, Sir, 1800-1890, 1825-64 (Box 18, Folder 892)
    - Baldwin, Stanley Baldwin, 1867-1947, undated (Box 18, Folder 893)
    - Balfour, Arthur James Balfour, Earl of, 1848-1930, 1890-1913, undated (Box 18, Folder 894)
    - Balfour of Burleigh, Alexander Hugh Bruce, Baron, 1849-1921, 1911 (Box 18, Folder 895)
    - Baring, Thomas, 1799-1873, 1867, undated (Box 18, Folder 896)
    - Barrington, George William, Viscount, 1824-1886, 1870, undated (Box 18, Folder 897)
    - Barrow, John, Sir, 1764-1848, 1811 (Box 18, Folder 898)
    - Bartlett, Ellis Ashmead, Sir, 1849- 1902, undated (Box 18, Folder 899)
    - Basing, George Sclater-Booth, Baron, 1826-1894, 1874-79 (Box 18, Folder 900)
    - Bath, Thomas Thynne, Marquis of, 1734- 1796, 1769 (Box 18, Folder 901)
    - Belhaven and Stenton, James, Lord, 1822-1893, 1864 (Box 18, Folder 902)
    - Bentinck, George Cavendish, 1821-1891, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 903)
    - Bentinck, George, Lord, 1802-1848, 1834-47 (Box 18, Folder 904)
    - Bentinck, Henry, Lord, 1804-1870, 1846 (Box 18, Folder 905)
    - Beresford, A.J.B. (Alexander James Beresford), 1820-1887, 1848-82, undated (Box 18, Folder 906)
    - Bergne, John Henry Gibbs, Sir, 1842- 1908, 1901 (Box 18, Folder 907)
    - Berkeley, Francis Henry Fitzhardinge, 1794-1870, 1845, undated (Box 18, Folder 908)
    - Beust, Friedrich Ferdinand, graf von, 1809-1886, undated (Box 18, Folder 909)
    - Bicheno, J.E. (James Ebenezer), 1785- 1851, undated (Box 18, Folder 910)
    - Biddulph, Thomas Myddleton, Sir, 1809- 1878, 1866-68 (Box 18, Folder 911)
    - Bottomley, Horatio, 1860-1933, 1907-16, undated (Box 18, Folder 912)
    - Bourke, Robert, 1827-1902, undated (Box 18, Folder 913)
    - Bowring, John, Sir, 1792-1872, 1855-72 (Box 18, Folder 914)
    - Brabourne, Edward Hugessen Knatchbull- Hugessen, Baron, 1829-1893, 1890-91 (Box 18, Folder 915)
    - Bradford, George Augustus Frederick Henry, Earl, 1789-1863, 1839-60, undated (Box 18, Folder 916)
    - Bradford, George Cecil Orlando Bridgeman, Earl, 1845-1915, 1809 (Box 18, Folder 917)
    - Bradlaugh, Charles, 1833-1891, undated (Box 18, Folder 918)
    - Brand, Henry Bouverie, 1814-1892, 1862-71, undated (Box 18, Folder 919)
    - Brassey, Henry Arthur, 1840-1891, 1875 (Box 18, Folder 920)
    - Brassey, Thomas Brassey, Earl, 1836- 1918, 1879-1905 (Box 18, Folder 921)
    - Bright, John, 1811-1889, 1855-88 (Box 18, Folder 922)
    - Bristol, Frederick William Hervey, Marquis of, 1800-1864, 1851, undated (Box 18, Folder 923)
    - Bristol, Frederick William John, Marquess of, 1834-1907, 1873-95 (Box 18, Folder 924)
    - Brooke, James, Sir, 1803-1868, undated (Box 18, Folder 925)
    - Brougham, William, 1795-1886, 1874-78 (Box 18, Folder 926)
    - Brougham and Vaux, Henry Brougham, 1778-1868, 1866, undated (Box 18, Folder 927)
    - Brownlow, Adelbert Wellington Brownlow Cust, Earl, 1844-1921, 1893, undated (Box 18, Folder 928)
    - Bruce, Michael, 1787-1861, 1829-56, undated (Box 18, Folder 929)
    - Brunnow, Ernst Philipp, Count von, 1797-1875, 1819, undated (Box 18, Folder 930)
    - Bryce, James Bryce, Viscount, 1838- 1922, 1881 (Box 18, Folder 931)
    - Buccleuch, Walter Francis Scott, Duke of, 1806-1884, 1830-77, undated (Box 19, Folder 932)
    - Buccleuch, Walter Henry Walter Montagu-Douglas-Scott, Duke of, 1831- 1914, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 933)
    - Buckingham and Chandos, Richard Plantagenet Campbell Temple Nugent Brydges Chandos Grenville, Duke of, 1823-1889, 1841-87, undated (Box 19, Folder 934)
    - Buckingham and Chandos, Richard Plantagenet Temple Nugent Brydges Chandos Grenville, Duke of, 1797-1861, 1840-59, undated (Box 19, Folder 935)
    - Bunsen, Christian Karl Josias, Freiherr von, 1791-1868, 1850, undated (Box 19, Folder 936)
    - Burdett, Francis, Sir, 1770-1844, 1841, undated (Box 19, Folder 937)
    - Burns, John, 1858-1943, 1889 (Box 19, Folder 938)
    - Bute, John Stuart, Earl of, 1713-1792, undated (Box 19, Folder 939)
    - Canning, Charles John Canning, Earl, 1812-1862, undated (Box 19, Folder 940)
    - Canning, George, 1770-1827, 1815-27, undated (Box 19, Folder 941)
    - Capelle, Guillaume-Antoine-Benoit, Baron, 1775-1843, 1837 (Box 19, Folder 942)
    - Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, 1845-66 (Box 19, Folder 943)
    - Carlisle, George William Frederick Howard, Earl of, 1802-1864, 1846 (Box 19, Folder 944)
    - Carnarvon, Henry Howard Moylneux, Earl of, 1831-1890, 1883 (Box 19, Folder 945)
    - Carrington, Charles Robert, Lord, 1843-1928, 1883-91 (Box 19, Folder 946)
    - Cavagnari, Pierre Louis Napoleon, Sir, 1841-1879 (Box 19, Folder 947)
    - Cave, Stephen, 1820-1880, 1867-74, undated (Box 19, Folder 948)
    - Chamberlain, Joseph, 1836-1914, 1876 (Box 19, Folder 949)
    - Chelmsford, Frederick Thesiger, Baron, 1794-1878, 1842-66, undated (Box 19, Folder 950)
    - Chesham, Charles Compton Cavendish, Lord, 1793-1863, undated (Box 19, Folder 951)
    - Chicago Progressive National Convention, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 952)
    - Childers, Hugh C.E. (Hugh Culling Eardley), 1827-1896, 1869-93, undated (Box 19, Folder 953)
    - Churchill, Randolph Henry Spencer, Lord, 1849-1895, undated (Box 19, Folder 954)
    - Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870, 1845-65 (Box 19, Folder 955)
    - Cottenham, Charles Christopher Pepys, Earl of, 1781-1851, 1838, undated (Box 19, Folder 956)
    - Cowley, Henry Richard Charles Wellesley, Earl, 1804-1884, 1840-56 (Box 19, Folder 957)
    - Cromer, Evelyn Baring, Earl of, 1841- 1917, 1894-1909 (Box 19, Folder 958)
    - Delano, Charles, 1820-1883, 1870 (Box 19, Folder 959)
    - Derby, Edward George Geoffrey Smith Stanley, Earl of, 1799-1869, 1836 (Box 19, Folder 960)
    - Derby, Edward Henry Stanley, Earl of, 1826-1893, 1862-89 (Box 19, Folder 961)
    - Devonshire, Spencer Compton Cavendish, Duke of, 1833-1908, 1858-85 (Box 19, Folder 962)
    - Dilke, Charles Wentworth, Sir, 1843- 1911, 1884-98, undated (Box 19, Folder 963)
    - Disraeli, Benjamin, Earl of Beaconsfield, 1804-1881, 1867-1913, undated (Box 19, Folder 964)
    - Dix, John A. (John Adams), 1798-1879, 1845-74 (Box 19, Folder 965)
    - Drew, Mary Gladstone, 1847-1927, 1889 (Box 19, Folder 966)
    - Drummond-Hay, undated (Box 19, Folder 967)
    - Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860, 1843 (Box 19, Folder 968)
    - Duncombe, Thomas Slingsby, 1796-1861, 1846-53, undated (Box 19, Folder 969)
    - Dungannon, Arthur Hill-Trevor, Viscount, 1798-1862, 1859 (Box 19, Folder 970)
    - Durham, George Lambton, Earl of, 1828- 1879 (also includes Herschell, Farrer, Baron), 1877 (Box 19, Folder 971)
    - Dyke, William Hart, Sir, 1837-1931, undated (Box 19, Folder 972)